Viacheslav Chopyk

Front End Web Developer

Email: if040489cvv@gmail.com

Skype: if040489cvv

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/viacheslav-chopyk-735622170/

Personal Page: https://chopyk89.github.io/portfolio

Profile

Front End Web Developer with near 1 year of commercial experience in software development mostly using Angular Framework. Familiarized with cross-browser and cross-device responsive web development. Result-orientated, responsible and attention to details. During this time I had the opportunities to work with several types of projects:

Healthcare - platform healthier working environment. Internet 3D market - creating Iframe external plugin with 3D Internet of Things - platform of manage light in building E-commerce - platform of booking

Creating mobile apps with Angular.

Also had experience as mentor, reviewer of code or lead of front-end team on the project, creating architecture of project and project structure from scratch.

Technical Skills

Category	Skill list
Programming languages	JavaScript, TypeScript
Operating systems	Windows, Ubuntu, MacOS, Android, IOS
Libraries	Angular Material, AngularJS Material, ZingChart, Angular Bootstrap, UI-Cropper, Angular Paging, Angular Translate, RxJs, Lodash, Sweetalert, ngx-translate, Moment.JS, Moment-timezone, ng-color, ng- pick-datatime, ngx-mat-select-search, Chart.js, angular-calendar, date- fns, bootstrap 4, JQuery, Google maps, Formspree, NGRX, NGXS, Formspree, Bootstrap, WebGL, Husky, ngx-spinner, ng-image-slider, prettier, ngx-infinite-scroll, an-qrcode
Technologies	Angular 2 +, AngularJS,
Development tools	Google DevTools, Avocode, Figma, Adobe Creative Cloud, WebStorm, VS Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Android Studio, Gulp, Xcode
RDBMS	SQL, POSTGRESQL
Web	HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JADE, PUG,

SCM	Git, GitLab, Github, Bitbucket
BTS	Redmine, Trello, Jira, Gitlab board

Education

2006 - 2012

Ivano-Frankivsk National Technical University of Oil and Gas Institute of Humanities and Public Administration Graduation degree specialist of documentation and information activities Ivano-Frankivsk, Ukraine

Languages

• English — Intermediate

• Ukrainian — Native

Working experience

November 2021 – present Ivano Frankivsk, Ukraine

Dates: 13 November 2021 - Present

Role: Front-End Developer

About project: Several web sites (service), with ability to configure and buy 2D/3D models of furniture. Plugin iframe in customer site.Platform that speeds up the whole process of furniture configuration and selling. It simplifies the process of ordering and selling furniture by using interactive 3D and AR technologies. Platform allows you to change colors in real time, materials, add or remove furniture elements and get the price instantly

Description: Change design and write or rewrite JavaScript/TypeScript, creating new projects, pages, architectures, writing custom: services, pipes, modal windows, Iframe plugins, mobile responsive, working with Unity (WebGL), bug fixing.